Department of Music Records UA017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Musical scores, 1880 -- 1970; UA017.003; 7.2 Linear Feet
  - Forward, Tufts!, 1907; UA017.003.005.00020 (Box 5)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis. Words by D. L. Maulsly.
  - Four-Part Analysis, 1921 -- 1940; UA017.003.005.00021 (Box 5)
    Composed by R. R. Lamont.
  - Four Songs, Opus 3, 1903; UA017.003.005.00022 (Box 5)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Song is also called "The Waterlily."
  - Freshman Lay, "Just Sprouted", 1922; UA017.003.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Fughetta in C, on the initials G. C. B(ainum), 1944 -- 1945; UA017.003.005.00024 (Box 5)
    Written for Music 191 by L. R. Lewis.
  - Fugne, 1933; UA017.003.005.00025 (Box 5)
    Written for demonstration in Music 38-24 by L. R. Lewis.
  - Glee Club Copies used in The Song Book, 1906; UA017.003.005.00026 (Box 5)
    Includes prompt cards from Glee Club performances.
  - Guard Old Glory, 1918; UA017.003.005.00027 (Box 5)
    Music in this folder by L. R. Lewis. Text by J. H. Earle.
  - Hard to Please, 1935 -- 1936; UA017.003.005.00028 (Box 5)
    Music in this folder by L. R. Lewis. Text by M. Howells. Original title was "The Difficult Seed."
  - The Heart of the World, 1896; UA017.003.005.00029 (Box 5)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by W. P. Foster.
  - Henning arrangements, 1960 -- 1970; UA017.003.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Holy Art Thou, 1914; UA017.003.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - The Hoodoo, 1900; UA017.003.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - I'm The Guy, 1912; UA017.003.005.00033 (Box 5)
    Composed by B. Grant. Text by R. Goldberg.
  - In Diesen Heil'gen Hallen, 1938; UA017.003.005.00034 (Box 5)
    This folder contains a copy of a score composed by F. F. Bullard.
  - The Indifferent Matter, 1898; UA017.003.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - In Gilbert and Sullivan Land, 1928; UA017.003.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Intercollegiate Inklings, 1927; UA017.003.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis
  - Inventions, etc., 1933; UA017.003.006.00002 (Box 6)
    This folder contains a piece of music used for Music 38-24.
  - I Sing the Man - A tribute to Professor Leo R. Lewis, 1900 -- 1945; UA017.003.006.00003 (Box 6)
    Composed by E. Newton.
  - In Memoriam, 1940; UA017.003.006.00004 (Box 6)
    Composed by E. W. Newton for his 50th Anniversary. Scored by L. R. Lewis.
  - Jack and the Baked Bean Stalk, 1880 -- 1920; UA017.003.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - The Jumbo Chant, 1925; UA017.003.006.00006 (Box 6)
    Glee Club arrangement composed by A. C. Gioler.
  - The Jumbo Strut, 1944; UA017.003.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Jumbo the Great, 1922; UA017.003.006.00008 (Box 6)
    Music and text by L. R. Lewis.
  - The Kaiseriole, 1919; UA017.003.006.00009 (Box 6)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis.
  - The Kavanaugh, 1904; UA017.003.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Kruglied (A Stein Song), 1898; UA017.003.006.00011 (Box 6)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Text by R. Hovey. Translated by F. Vogel.
  - Lass of Norwichtown, 1899; UA017.003.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Let All That Seek Thee, 1937; UA017.003.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Lilt from Suite, College Life, 1900 -- 1920; UA017.003.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Little Willie, 1908; UA017.003.006.00015 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. L. Hall.
  - The Lord is My Shepherd, 1952; UA017.003.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - The Lost Chord, 1901; UA017.003.006.00017 (Box 6)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Words by A. A. Proctor.
  - Love Came Down From Out the Sky, 1902; UA017.003.006.00018 (Box 6)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by W. Packard.
  - Love Me, Love Me Not, 1905; UA017.003.006.00019 (Box 6)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by R. Hovey.
  - Loyalty Song (Jackson College), 1900 -- 1920; UA017.003.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Madrigal, 1900 -- 1920; UA017.003.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Mariar! Mariar!, 1895; UA017.003.006.00022 (Box 6)
    Composed by W. Packard.
  - Massachusetts There She Stands, 1930; UA017.003.006.00023 (Box 6)
    Composed by E. W. Hayes.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [1 of 5], 1930; UA017.003.006.00024 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. W. Morton. Printed conductor's score for symphonic orchestra.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [2 of 5], 1930; UA017.003.006.00025 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. W. Morton. Original conductor's score.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [3 of 5], 1914 -- 1935; UA017.003.006.00026 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. W. Morton. Conductor's score for symphonic orchestra, contains edits.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [4 of 5], 1913 -- 1915; UA017.003.006.00027 (Box 6)
    This piece was first played on Class Day 1913. Composed by J. W. Morton. Contains conductor's score for military band arrangement and individual instrument parts.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [5 of 5], 1935 -- 1936; UA017.003.006.00028 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. W. Morton. Contains symphonic orchestra arrangement, earlier drafts of parts.
  - M-M-M-M The Grandad Song, 1933; UA017.003.006.00029 (Box 6)
    Composed by R. C. Gioler.
  - A Modern Martyrdom, 1907; UA017.003.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Morton scores [original, orchestral, and other scores], 1910 -- 1935; UA017.003.006.00031 (Box 6)
    A majority of the pieces in this folder were composed by J. W. Morton.
  - My Auto, 1923; UA017.003.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - The Monk of the Mountain, 1900; UA017.003.006.00033 (Box 6)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard
  - New Hampshire music and band scores, 1920 -- 1923; UA017.003.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Nonsense Rhymes, 1898 -- 1905; UA017.003.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - North and South, 1918; UA017.003.006.00036 (Box 6)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis. Also contains the song "We Stand."
  - Norwegian Folk Song, 1924; UA017.003.006.00037 (Box 6)
    Composed by J. F. Gilder.
  - Old Fortunatus, 1906 -- 1937; UA017.003.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Old Hymn Arrangements, 1880 -- 1910; UA017.003.007.00002 (Box 7)
    The hymns in this folder were arranged by F. F. Bullard.
  - An Old-Time Celebration, 1915 -- 1923; UA017.003.007.00003 (Box 7)
    Composed by E. W. Newton. Also known as "Newton's March."
  - An Old-Time Celebration, 1915 -- 1923; UA017.003.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - An Old-Time Celebration, 1916; UA017.003.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - An Old-Time Celebration, 1923; UA017.003.007.00006 (Box 7)
    Composed by E. W. Newton and L. R. Lewis. Also known as "Newton's March."
  - Onward, Alma Mater, 1922 -- 1931; UA017.003.007.00007 (Box 7)
    Composed by R. R. Lamont. Folder also contains score for Onward, O New Hampshire.
  - Onward, O Tuftonia, 1963; UA017.003.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Opus 8 [The Singer], 1894; UA017.003.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - O Stern Old Land, 1913; UA017.003.007.00010 (Box 7)
    Music by F. F. Bullard. Words by C. E. Whiton-Stone.
  - Our College, 1890; UA017.003.007.00011 (Box 7)
    Composed by E. W. Newton.
  - A Patriotic Hymn: O Stern Old Land, 1895; UA017.003.007.00012 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by C. E. Whiton-Stone.
  - Pax et Lux, 1910; UA017.003.007.00013 (Box 7)
    Composed by H. E. Dow.
  - Pillage of Mars (War Profits), 1912 -- 1940; UA017.003.007.00014 (Box 7)
    Music by R. R. Lamont. Text by J. Roety.
  - Piano Quartet, 1892 -- 1909; UA017.003.007.00015 (Box 7)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis. Also titled "Quartett fuer Klavier, Violine, Bratsche und Violoncello" or "Opus 4."
  - Potpurri for "The Country Girl", 1924; UA017.003.007.00016 (Box 7)
    Composed by L. Moncklor.
  - Pre-1907 scores, 1880 -- 1907; UA017.003.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Quartet in A-minor, 1889; UA017.003.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Remind Me Sweeting, 1900; UA017.003.007.00019 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by R. Hovey. Also titled, "You Remind Me, Sweeting."
  - Reverie, 1940; UA017.003.007.00020 (Box 7)
    Arranged by R. R. Lamont. Composed by F. F. Bullard.
  - Ring Forth - Class Song of 1926, 1906 -- 1926; UA017.003.007.00021 (Box 7)
    Compsed by E. J. Wood. Text by M. S. Hall.
  - Robbins, Reginald C., songs, 1941; UA017.003.007.00022 (Box 7)
    This folder contains the following pieces composed by R. C. Robbins: "Lethe," "Advent," and "To One Born Last Night."
  - Rock of Ages, 1880; UA017.003.007.00023 (Box 7)
    Arranged by F. F. Bullard.
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1903 -- 1936; UA017.003.007.00024 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. N. Scott. Arranged for the Tufts 1903 Glee Club.
  - The Rose and the Ring, 1934 -- 1935; UA017.003.007.00025 (Box 7)
    Composed by C. B. Lewis. Orchestration by L. R. Lewis. Text by M. W. Kingsley.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Score for full orchestra], 1934; UA017.003.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - The Rose and the Ring [Score for orchestra], 1934; UA017.003.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - The Rose and the Ring [Rough score of the second act], 1934; UA017.003.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - The Rose of Kenmore, 1901; UA017.003.007.00029 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Text by A. P. Graves.
  - Sail On, 1930; UA017.003.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Sea Song, 1911 -- 1914; UA017.003.007.00031 (Box 7)
    Remembered by S. Loomis.
  - Sea Song [Glee Club arrangement], 1910 -- 1914; UA017.003.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - See Old Glory, 1918; UA017.003.007.00033 (Box 7)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis. Text by J. H. Earle.
  - Selections from The Quaker Girl, 1912; UA017.003.007.00034 (Box 7)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by L. Morickton.
  - Sempre Giovine (Always Young), 1900; UA017.003.007.00035 (Box 7)
    Composed by E. Brooks.
  - Siegmund's Love Story from Die Walkuere, 1906 -- 1916; UA017.003.007.00036 (Box 7)
    Arranged for organ by R. R. Lamont. Composed by R. Wagner.
  - The Singer, 1933; UA017.003.007.00037 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Revised by L. R. Lewis and C. B. Lewis.
  - The Sisters (A Ballad), 1880 -- 1900; UA017.003.007.00038 (Box 7)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Text by A. Tennyson.
  - Six Songs From the German for Low Voices, 1892; UA017.003.007.00039 (Box 7)
    Composed and translated by F. F. Bullard.
  - Sketches of unfinished things, 1925 -- 1931; UA017.003.007.00040 (Box 7)
    The pieces in the folder were composed by R. L. Lamont.
  - Some Little Boy, 1916 -- 1923; UA017.003.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Sonate fuer Klavier und Violine, 1890; UA017.003.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Song of the Awakening [Arranged for Band], 1936; UA017.003.007.00043 (Box 7)
    Music by R. R. Lamont. Text by J. Rorty.
  - Song of the Awakening [Arranged for Piano], 1936; UA017.003.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Song of the Flag, 1944; UA017.003.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Songs for High Voices, 1889 -- 1890; UA017.003.007.00046 (Box 7)
    This book is water-damaged and contains inactive black mold. Songs composed by F. F. Bullard.
  - Songs for Low Voices, 1889 -- 1890; UA017.003.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Speak Kindly, 1914 -- 1941; UA017.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
    This folder also contains the piece, Spell It Out. Arranged by L. R. Lewis for Tufts Glee Club. Composed by A. T. Williams.
  - Spell It Out (for Tufts), 1920 -- 1921; UA017.003.008.00002 (Box 8)
    Composed by A. T. Williams. One piece in this folder was arranged by E. W. Hayes.
  - A Stein Song, 1889; UA017.003.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - String Quartet, 1880 -- 1920; UA017.003.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - String Quartet in A-minor, 1887 -- 1939; UA017.003.008.00005 (Box 8)
    This folder contains arrangements by R. R. Lamont and compositions by F. F. Bullard.
  - String Quartet in E-flat, 1890; UA017.003.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Sword of Ferrara, 1899; UA017.003.008.00007 (Box 8)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by M. McLennan.
  - Sword of Ferrara, 1912 -- 1926; UA017.003.008.00008 (Box 8)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by M. McLennan. Some compositions are water-damaged.
  - Swords Out For Charlie, 1901; UA017.003.008.00009 (Box 8)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Words by R. A. Cram
  - Symphonic Prelude to Robert Browning's A Blot in the Scrutcheon., 1909 -- 1924; UA017.003.008.00010 (Box 8)
    Composed by L. R. Lewis. The pieces contained in this folder have some water-damage.
  - Symphony in D-minor, 1891; UA017.003.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Symphony in D-minor, 1891 -- 1892; UA017.003.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Symphony in D-minor [F. F. Bullard's copy], 1891 -- 1892; UA017.003.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Te Salutamus, 1936; UA017.003.008.00014 (Box 8)
    Composed by K. MacKillop, Jr. and L. R. Lewis.
  - That Mascot, 1914 -- 1924; UA017.003.008.00015 (Box 8)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by P. B. Lewis.
  - That's Why [Extras], 1930; UA017.003.008.00016 (Box 8)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by N. S. Bean
  - That's Why [For Orchestra], 1930 -- 1936; UA017.003.008.00017 (Box 8)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by N. S. Bean.
  - Theme with Variegations, 1945; UA017.003.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - There is One Way and Only One Way, 1899; UA017.003.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - There's a Woman Like a Dewdrop, 1901; UA017.003.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Three Cavalier Songs, 1901; UA017.003.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Three Cheers For Your Uncle Sam, 1917 -- 1918; UA017.003.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Three Cheers For Your Uncle Sam - March with chorus, 1917; UA017.003.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Three-Part Invention IX - Harmonic Scheme, 1906; UA017.003.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Thy Will Be Done!, 1903; UA017.003.008.00025 (Box 8)
    Arranged by F. F. Bullard. Composed by Mendelssohn. Text by J. Roscoe.
  - Tick-Tack-Too, 1903 -- 1937; UA017.003.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Toreador, Hola, 1911; UA017.003.008.00027 (Box 8)
    This score has sustained some water-damage. Composed by H. Trotere. Arranged by N. Clifford Page and L. R. Lewis. Words by C. Bingham.
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody [1 of 3], 1916 -- 1940; UA017.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody [2 of 3], 1938 -- 1940; UA017.003.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody [3 of 3], 1938 -- 1939; UA017.003.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1915 -- 1921; UA017.003.009.00004 (Box 9)
    Composed by E. H. Hayes.
  - Tufts '90 Goes to Town, 1890 -- 1940; UA017.003.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Tufts College Class of 1887 - Class Song and Ode, UA017.003.009.00006 (Box 9)
    Music by L. R. Lewis. Text by C. H. Patterson.
  - Tufts Glee Club prompt books, 1905 -- 1907; UA017.003.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Song Book, 1906; UA017.003.009.00008 (Box 9)
    book
  - Tufts songbook, 1930 -- 1950; UA017.003.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Tufts songbook, 1930 -- 1950; UA017.003.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Songs, 1895; UA017.003.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Songs, 1901; UA017.003.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Songs, 1915; UA017.003.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Text - Melody collection for the Class Day guests of 1922, UA017.003.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Today, Tufts For Aye, 1915 -- 1927; UA017.003.009.00015 (Box 9)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by W. G. Brooks.
  - Twilight - Andante from Opus 7, 1937; UA017.003.009.00016 (Box 9)
    Arranged by R. H. Milne. Composed by E. Grieg.
  - Union and Liberty, 1902; UA017.003.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - The United States to Great Britain, 1940 -- 1942; UA017.003.009.00018 (Box 9)
    Composed by W. E. Young. Text by M. B. Eddy.
  - The Unknown, 1935; UA017.003.009.00019 (Box 9)
    Composed by B. Huhn. Text by W. Whitman.
  - Up to Date, 1905; UA017.003.009.00020 (Box 9)
    Arranged by J. R. Wyckoff and W. Vreeland.
  - Various styles on Concert Overture, 1900; UA017.003.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Victory Song, 1909 -- 1932; UA017.003.009.00022 (Box 9)
    Arranged by L. R. Lewis. Composed by W. W. Rose.
  - The Waterlily, 1893; UA017.003.009.00023 (Box 9)
    composed by F. F. Bullard. Also known as "Opus 3."
  - We Stand - A song of devotion to the United States, 1918; UA017.003.009.00024 (Box 9)
    Music by L. R. Lewis. Text by C. D. Platt.
  - We Stand [Score for full orchestra], 1918; UA017.003.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - When Doctors Disagree, 1911 -- 1914; UA017.003.009.00026 (Box 9)
    Music by L. R. Lewis.
  - Where 'er You Walk, 1928 -- 1938; UA017.003.009.00027 (Box 9)
    Arranged by R. R. Lamont. Composed by Handel.
  - When the Little Ones Say Good Night, 1912; UA017.003.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Where To Go To, 1913; UA017.003.009.00029 (Box 9)
    Composed by M. H. Merrill. Also referred to as "The Go-To Song."
  - Wise Old Neptune, 1910 -- 1930; UA017.003.009.00030 (Box 9)
    Music by C. B. Lewis. Text by R. B. Lawrence. The score in this folder is water-damaged and contains inactive black mold.
  - You Remind Me, Sweeting, 1915; UA017.003.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - You Remind Me, Sweeting - Serenade, 1900; UA017.003.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - You Shall Not Go, 1899; UA017.003.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Zwei 4-stimmige Lieder, 1889 -- 1890; UA017.003.009.00034 (Box 9)
    Composed by F. F. Bullard. Text by R. Reinick.
- Faculty, staff and student files and scrapbooks, circa 1830 -- 1984; 1954 -- 1993; UA017.004; 2.76 Linear Feet
  This series contains the personal papers and scrapbooks of Music Department faculty, staff, and students from 1921 to 1985. The scrapbooks and files of Prof. Leo R. Lewis A1887 H1922 make up a majority of the material. Leo R. Lewis' materials include correspondence, event invitations, curricula vitae, essays, reports, obituaries, course plans and curriculum outlines, biographical sketches and employment records, as well as two scrapbooks; one containing Boston-area concert programs from 1889-1899, and a scrapbook of to-do lists and materials for French and Music Department courses. Leo R. Lewis' effects also include an invitation to the dedication of the Wagner Memorial in 1903, information on the Bowen Chimes, as well as sheet music for violin and other instruments, performance sets from the Tufts Mandolin Club, music manuscripts, and other material created or collected by Lewis and his brother in law Frederick Field Bullard. Also included are materials from Richard R. Lamont A1911, including resumes, reunion materials (Class of 1911), event programs from Goddard Seminary, and an essay on the study of modern languages. This series also includes an obituary for Carrie Bullard Lewis, and a small biographical sketch of Philip B. Lewis A1922, as well as Rev. Willis A. Moore's correspondence with President Hamilton of Tufts.
  This series is arranged alphabetically and by order of accession.
  - [Lamont, Richard Roy - Class of 1911], 1936 -- 1941; UA017.004.015.00009 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
    This folder contains information on R. R. Lamont's reunions for the Class of 1911.
  - [Lamont, Richard Roy - Academic records and Study of Modern Languages], 1929; UA017.004.015.00010 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - [Lamont, Richard Roy - Goddard Seminary publications and programs], 1909 -- 1914; UA017.004.015.00011 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - [Lamont, Richard Roy - Tufts correspondence], 1963 -- 1976; UA017.004.015.00012 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
    This correspondence originated from R.R. Lamont's vertical file, compiled by Russell Miller.
  - Lamont, Richard R - Personal data, 1966 -- 1977; UA017.004.015.00013 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Carrie Bullard (Mrs. Leo R. Lewis), 1951 -- 1952; UA017.004.015.00014 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
    This material was originally a vertical file, compiled by Russell Miller.
  - Lewis, Leo R. [1 of 6], 1915 -- 1945; UA017.004.015.00015 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
    This material was originally a vertical file, compiled by Russell Miller. This folder contains a detailed biographical sketch of Leo R. Lewis.
  - Lewis, Leo R. [2 of 6], 1894 -- 1945; UA017.004.015.00016 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Leo R. [3 of 6], 1910 -- 1933; UA017.004.015.00017 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Leo R. [4 of 6], 1933 -- 1984; UA017.004.015.00018 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Leo R. [5 of 6], 1918 -- 1945; UA017.004.015.00019 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
    This folder contains a brief history of Tufts Music. This material was originally a vertical file, compiled by Russell Miller.
  - Lewis, Leo R. [6 of 6] Invitation to the dedication of the monument to Richard Wagner, 1903; UA017.004.015.00020 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Leo R. sample copyright cards, 1915 -- 1942; UA017.004.015.00021 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Lewis, Philip, 1946 -- 1961; UA017.004.015.00022 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Moore, Willis H., 1908; UA017.004.015.00023 (Box UA017 Shared 1)
  - Leo R. Lewis' concert scrapbook, 1889 -- 1899; UA017.004.016.00001 (Box 16)
    This scrapbook contains programs and ticket stubs from concerts and music events that took place in and around Boston.
  - Leo R. Lewis' scrapbook, 1909 -- 1945; UA017.004.016.00002 (Box 16)
    This scrapbook contains office files, correspondence, course materials for the Music Department and the French Department, and music programs.
  - Leo R. Lewis' scrapbook, 1945; UA017.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
    Scrapbook; Lewis, Leo R.
  - Leo R. Lewis' collected sheet music, circa 1830 -- 1945; UA017.004.019; .75 Linear Feet
    Transferred by staff of the Tufts Lilly Music Library, 2018, accession UA-2019-047.
    This file contains sheet music for violin and other instruments, performance sets from the Tufts Mandolin Club, music manuscripts, and other material created or collected by Leo Rich Lewis, Tufts graduate and Fletcher Professor of Music, and his brother in law Frederick Field Bullard.
    Lewis, Leo R.
- Leo R. Lewis's piano, 1898; UA017.005; 1 Artifact(s)
  This series consists of an upright piano made by Henry F. Miller pianos in Boston. This was the piano where Leo Rich Lewis composed the song, "Dear Alma Mater" in 1898.
  This series contains one item.
  - Leo Lewis' piano, 1898; UA017.005.017.00001 (Box 17)
    Dear Alma Mater composed at this piano by Leo Rich Lewis in 1898. This piano was previously cataloged under MS012 - The Leo R. Lewis Collection. This collection was merged with UA017 in June 2010.
    Artifacts (object genre); Lewis, Leo R.
- Additional accessions, 1950; UA017.006
  - William J. King photographs, score, and Band patches, 1950; UA017-001 (Box data_value_missing_0e639533b9500665aed3e98ea2ccfd8d, Box 1)